[
    {
        "front": "にげます|| ",
        "back": "run away",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "さわぎます| ",
        "back": "make a noise",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "あきらめます||",
        "back": "give up",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "なげます||",
        "back": "throw",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "まもります| ",
        "back": "keep, follow, obey",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "はじまります|\n［しきが～］",
        "back": "[a ceremony] begin, start",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅっせきします|||\n［かいぎに～］",
        "back": "attend [a meeting]",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "つたえます|| ",
        "back": "convey ",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅういします|||\n［くるまに～］ ",
        "back": "be carefull (of the cars)",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "はずします|\n［せきを～］ ",
        "back": "be away (from one's desk)",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "もどります|",
        "back": "come back, return",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "あります|\n［でんわが～］ ",
        "back": "have [a telephone call]",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "リサイクルします|||",
        "back": "recycle",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "だめ［な］ ",
        "back": "no good, not permitted, impossible",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "おなじ",
        "back": "same",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "けいさつ ",
        "back": "police (station)",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "せき ",
        "back": "seat",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "マーク ",
        "back": "mark, symbol",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "ボール ",
        "back": "ball",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "しめきり",
        "back": "deadline",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "きそく ",
        "back": "regulation, rule",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "きけん",
        "back": "Danger",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "しようきんし ",
        "back": "Do not use",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "たちいりきんし",
        "back": "Keep Out",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "じょこう",
        "back": "Go Slow",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "いりぐち ",
        "back": "entrance",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "でぐち ",
        "back": "exit",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "ひじょうぐち ",
        "back": "emergency exit",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "むりょう ",
        "back": "Free of Charge",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "わりびき",
        "back": "Discount",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "のみほうだい",
        "back": "All You Can Drink",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "しようちゅう ",
        "back": "In Use",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "ぼしゅうちゅう",
        "back": "Applications Wanted",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "～ちゅう ",
        "back": "~ing",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "どういう～ ",
        "back": "what (kind of ~)",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "もう ",
        "back": "(not) any longer (used with negatives)",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "あと～ ",
        "back": "~left",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "～ほど",
        "back": "about~",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうしゃいはん ",
        "back": "parking violation",
        "chapter": 33
    },
    {
        "front": "ばっきん ",
        "back": "fine",
        "chapter": 33
    }
]
